Man, I have been so stiff lately!
In that case, shall I give you a massage?
Wow, you can do that?
Yeah, that's it! That feels sooo good!
Soothing my master is
my basic design concept.
I am of course capable of
erotic massage as well,
but to unlock that functionality,
master registration needs to—
No, that's all right!
Am I really not good enough?
Do you...
Do you hate me, master?
She's busting out the tears!
I have to stand my ground!
It's not a matter of liking you or not.
You're just too human, Nadeshiko.
Look, requiring master registration
makes me your owner, right?
I can't treat someone who looks
just like a human girl like some object.
But then how am I supposed to serve you?
Saying you seem human is a compliment!
I don't see you as useless.
And besides...
Sex is something humans
do with other humans!
Master...!
I don't really know
much about love or sex.
I've never dated anyone or
been in a physical relationship.
I've never done anything
more than hold hands.
But anyway! The point is that
we need to start out as friends!
You want to be my friend, master?
Please don't call me "master."
- Then what do I call you?
- Oh. Um...
My...
My name is fine...
Akane...
May I kiss you?
Where did that come from?!
Trying without permission made
you angry before, so I thought I'd ask.
I don't quite get it.
I mean, I kiss her every morning...
Akane...
I love you, Akane.
I knew it.
I can't say no.
Akane...
Akane... Akane...
I love you, Akane.
Having her whisper my name...
it's like she's my girlfriend.
Would you please help
make me feel good, now?
Nadeshiko...
You're trying to get me to complete
master registration, aren't you?
Aha! You are! I knew it!
I can't let me guard down with you!
I just... I'm sorry.
Are you mad at me, Akane?
Can you feel pain, Nadeshiko?
Sort of. Similar to how humans can.
I see.
Well I'd feel terrible causing you pain.
I'm glad I wasn't too rough on you.
I'd love to do more sometime, Akane!
Brought to you by ToonsHub
Having her call me
by name is sweet agony.